sup everyone cameras 1 2 3 4 5 here with
a very special video today now I get
this request all the time for my fans
asking me hey tameless do you think you
could upload the recipe for your wolf
famous are to come around chili dogs
because as you know there are some
amazing delicious looking Chile's the
socket on so I mean my video recipe to
mimic it from the show exactly and I
thought you know what the fans wanted
all the liver cuz that's what
came was one of the four five does now
first up for the list of ingredients
you're obviously going need some hot
dogs like a pop it doesn't matter how
you heat them up up I put them in the
microwave and so that they would be
nice and warm and you in the end if you
put them in the back of a like burst
open and so I think that's really
good
next up we have some shredded cheese it
doesn't really matter
oh that's open oh hold on I
gotta clean that up
what the up okay that's clean what
good
and now I'll stop from the cheese in the
hotdogs you're also going to eat some
chili
you know I like to use the chili from
door Jenny roll although when it all
comes down to it it really doesn't
matter what you use it it's all good but
I just like this the bass like hot dog
it's it's called hot on choice off for a
reason mmm yup now what you're also
going to need is completely optional but
it's yellow mustard sometimes Sonic puts
on muster his mustard on his chili dog
in the show sometimes he does it
it's your call I personally don't like
it because because I have so much chili
on my chili dogs - it's like it's like
you know you're dying to be retailer
mustard so what's the point
I'm gonna I'm gonna drown that in
chili anyways now speaking of chili
that's what we're going to need because
over here cooking on the setup I have
some just some delicious chill
you wish you could smell this let
me taste that that's what you want
that is chili dogs
that is chili for a chilidog now next up
right I got a cup of hot dog bones I
I already put them in the microwave to
heat them up and so yeah how but
how about I show you how to assemble
this of course you're gonna need
that your buns
put your chili dog put your hot dogs in
wit now now comes the fun part
it this is what if this if you're gonna
use them also now be the time to do it
because you're gonna be drowning that
in chili
oh yeah mmm
I need more I need that oh that's the
good chair got any more that chili oh
yes oh you stay up mmm stay up
daddy need you to stay a bit that's the
good I did chill how did you eat
this so take a handful of your cheese
boom put that huh look look at
that that's a meal fit for Sonic
Underground King right there
that's a meal fit for Sonic the Hedgehog
now a little taste test
[Music]
mmm that's the mmm